Imagine this is you
The setup, straight into it.
Imagine this is you.
Again,
we're building curiosity here by saying,
how can I relate to a goldfish?
And this is your life.
Now you're calling my life a water tank
where a fish lives?
Like most people's lives, there
are problems that can make it toxic.
Suddenly,
we've got a dash of relatability.
Other people have toxic lives
and issues that are happening.
If a fish is living in a toxic
environment, eventually it gets sick, so
you take her out of the dirty water
and put her in a new tank for a while.
Fantastic transition. By the way, guys,
think for a second.
When we're talking about raising the
stakes, Dr.
Julie here has had to pollute a tank,
go away, empty it, fill it up, clean,
probably wipe it out a bit,
fill it with water, bring it back,
move over to the
side, bring it back in,
start the edit for that transition.
The effort that she would've had to have
put in here for this, unless she had two
tanks. Well,
she had to buy a tank in the first place.
I very much doubt
that she's got a fish sitting in a plastic
bag on the kitchen
side so she can make this video.
She's probably got a house full of props.
I'm listening.
I've got the emotive response from the
audio, but then at the
same time,
I've got something to look at with my
eyes.
It's like a perfect trifecta of attention